renesas.com 2007-08-26

# Renesas Technology - Privacy

  |  |  |   
  
---  
| Privacy|   
  
| Privacy on the Web|   

| Getting Started |   

| Legal|   

| Using Our Website|   

|  |  | ** Renesas Privacy Policy   
**  
---  
  
Due to changes in Japanese law governing privacy, Renesas has withdrawn from affiliation with TRUSTe. There have been no substantive changes to Renesas' Privacy Statement, however, and Renesas continues to abide by the requirements of the EU Safe Harbor. If you have any questions or concerns, please utilize the contact information noted at the end of the Privacy Statement.  
  
## I. Policy on Personal Information Protection  
  
Renesas Technology Corp. (hereafter "Renesas"), as a semiconductor manufacturer aiming to be the leader in the "ubiquitous age," has absolute respect for the value of personal information on our customers, partner companies, officers, and employees (including contractors, corporate advisors, part-time employees, and temporary employees). Accordingly, Renesas is making the effort to establish and enforce a strict management system of such personal information protection.

The policy on personal information protection that is stipulated as follows and herein is to be promulgated to officers and employees, and enforced.

| [Compliance with laws and regulations]  
---  
1.| Renesas complies with laws and other regulations related to personal information protection.  
[Establishment and Implementation of Regulations Related to Personal Information]  
2.| As well as ensuring that its officers and employees recognize the importance of protecting personal information, using such information properly, and establishing regulations concerning the protection of personal information that is to be protected, Renesas steadily enforces, maintains, and continuously improves the regulations.  
[Legal Acquisition, Usage, and Provision of Personal Information]  
3.| Renesas handles the acquisition of personal information and the usage and provision of acquired personal information in due compliance with the prescribed regulations. If the disclosure, correction, deletion, stop usage of, or stop provision to third party of personal information is requested by a given person, Renesas respects that person's rights in relation to personal information and responds in due compliance with the prescribed regulation.  
[Implementation of Security Management for Personal Information]  
4.| In order to ensure the accuracy and security of personal information, Renesas complies with the prescribed regulations, controls access to personal information, curbs ways of taking personal information, and enforces measures for security management and necessary corrective measures such as the prevention of unauthorized access. Also, Renesas implements the necessary and appropriate measures to prevent the loss, destruction, falsification, and leakage of personal information.  
  
Satoru Ito

President & CEO

Renesas Technology Corp.

April 1, 2005  
  
## II. Purpose-of-use  
  
| (1)| Regarding contracts and business deals with customers and partner companies, Renesas uses personal information provided by the customers and partner companies.  
---|---  
(2)| Renesas uses personal information in order to provide beneficial and appropriate information, such as on goods and services handled by Renesas(*1) and the introduction of related services.  
(3)| Renesas may use personal information entrusted to it by partner companies within the scope of business operations.  
  
*1: Goods and services handled by Renesas are:

  1. semiconductor devices, semiconductor integrated circuits, and development, design, manufacturing, sales, maintenance of semiconductor integrated circuits and parts in which semiconductor devices and semiconductor integrated circuits are embedded;
  2. development, design, manufacturing, sale, and maintenance of software for relating to semiconductor integrated circuits; and
  3. any and all businesses pertaining to or relating to all of the foregoing items.

## III. Procedures for Requesting Disclosure and/or Other Actions  
  
**1\. Actions that May be Requested**

According to the law regarding personal information protection (herein "the law"), disclosure and/or other actions concerning personal data(*2) held by Renesas can be requested.

*2: "Disclosure and/or other actions concerning personal data" means the following items.

  * Providing a purpose-of-use
  * Disclosure of maintained personal data
  * Correction, addition, or deletion of content
  * Stop of usage
  * Stop of provision to third parties

**2\. Flow of Requests for Disclosure and/or Other Actions**

Please select either a. or b. below.

| a.| If you know the Renesas contact window at which your personal information is registered and provided (hereafter "registration window"):  
---|---  
→| Please contact the registration window. As the procedure for disclosure and/or other actions, please follow that set by the given registration window.  
b.| If you do not know the registration window:  
→| Since the request will be dealt with by the Office of Personal Information Protection specified under IV below, please proceed as described in sections 3 to 5 below.  
  
**3\. Request for Disclosure and/or Other Actions: Method of Application and Written Form to be Submitted**

(1)| Method of Application  
---|---  
  
In order to assure support and avoid trouble such as information leakage caused by imposters, requests for disclosure and/or other actions can only be accepted **in writing and through the postal system**. Please mail completed application forms to the postal address in (3) below by delivery-certified mail (210 Japanese yen as of January 31, 2005). The delivery-certified mail will be at your expense.

When the documents are sent from overseas via the international postal system, the expense will vary from country to country. Since we must rigorously confirm the identity of the requesting party, please understand that we will not reply to any requests via telephone, e-mail, fax, or in the form of a direct visit to our offices.  
  
(2)| Written form to be submitted  
(A) "Request for Disclosure and/or Other Actions Concerning Personal Information"  
(B) Written document to confirm identity of requesting party (or representative)  
(3)| Postal address  
  
Office of Personal Information Protection, Renesas Technology Corp.  
Marunouchi Building 34F, 2-4-1 Marunouchi, Chiyoda-ku, Tokyo 100-6334  
  
**4\. Written Form to Identify a Registered Individual or Representative**

In requesting disclosure and/or other actions, please submit a document identifying the requesting party's address and name. This prevents the leakage of personal information. If a representative is requesting the action, documentation to identify both the individual and his/her representative is required.  
Also, when the requesting individual is under 15 years of age, please have his/her representative request the action(s). The below list covers the various documents accepted as identification. In addition, all documents physically mailed to Renesas will be returned with the written reply from Renesas.

[Documents to Identify a Registered Individual]  
A copy of any of the following documents within its period of validity is required (note: images obtained by digital still cameras or scanners and print-outs thereof are excluded).

  * Driver's license  
_Note: If the home address has been changed, please attach a copy of the back of the license after having completed the procedure for recording a change of address._
  * Employee's ID card, student's ID card, or the official student's handbook
  * Utility bill
  * Basic Resident's Registration card  
_Note: Type B, in which name, date of birth, and address (current address) are recorded and a photo of the face is included, is required. In case of changes of home address within the same city, ward, town or village, a copy of the back of the card is also required._
  * Passport  
_Note: Copies of both the page which includes a photo and which carries the name, address, and other information are required._
  * Pension/annuity book
  * Welfare book
  * Health insurance card  
_Note: Ensure that the current address is entered in the address section._
  * Original foreigner's registration card or certificate of items listed on original foreigner's registration card (for non-Japanese residents)

[Documentation to identify a representative]  
Any of the following documents, issued within the last three months, is required.

  * If the representative has a parental right _(Civil Law, Article 818)_   
A document to prove this relationship with the individual
  * If the representative is a guardian of an adult _(Civil Law, Articles 8 and 843)_   
Certificate of registration
  * If the representative is a guardian of a minor _(Civil Law, Articles 839 and 840)_   
Certificate of registration
  * If the desired representative is not as listed above _(note: only acceptable if the requesting individual is over 15 years of age)_   
Original letter giving power of attorney, including the registered individual's signature and seal (For letter from overseas, signature only)

[If the guardian of an adult is an legal entity]  
Certified copy of a register, certified extract from the register, certificate with all the current listed items, or certificate of some listed items is required (note: the document has to have been issued within the last three months).

**5\. Service Charge and Method of Payment**

Requests for disclosure incur a service charge, in line with Article 30 of the law. Please transfer 800 Japanese yen (tax included) as a service charge to the bank account indicated below. Any transfer fee will be at the expense of the person making the request.  
However, the actual processing of corrections, stop of usage, and stop of provision to third parties is free of charge. Since our search for the requested personal information and the reply to the requesting party follow confirmation that the above amount has been deposited, please avoid errors in both the deposited amount and in the submitted documents.  
Please understand that we cannot refund the transferred service charge, even if the search results do not include the requested personal information, or if the requested personal information cannot be specified due to a drastic deficiency in the submitted documents.  
Furthermore, please understand that we are unable to accept direct payment of the service charge at our office, whether by the registered individual or by a representative.

Destination of transfer:

| Head office of Mizuho Corporate Bank, Ltd.  
---|---  
  
Account type:

| Checking account  
  
Account No.:

| 7850513  
  
Account holder:

| Renesas Technology Corp.  
  
**6\. Reply**

We will reply within 15 business days of the date on which transfer of the service charge is completed. However, please understand that our reply may be later than this if the days fall within the Japanese New Year holidays, spring break, or summer break.  
  
## IV. Contact Point for Questions, Complaints, and Consultation  
  
Contact us according to the details below with any questions, complaints, or requests for consultation with regard to the handling of personal information by us.

>>Please click [here](https://secure-resource.renesas.com/lib/eng/privacy/form.html) to go to the inquiry form.

|  | Office of Personal Information Protection, Renesas Technology, Corp.  
---|---  
Address: Nippon Bldg, 2-6-2 Otemachi, Chiyoda-ku, Tokyo 100-0004  
Phone No.: +81-3-3270-0900  
Business hours: 9:00-12:00 and 13:00-17:00 (Japan Time)  
  
<% if(fileBodyNav.exists()) { %> <%}%>   |
